Guess what time it is.
猜猜现在是什么时间
&gt;&gt; Time for more cake.
现在是吃蛋糕的时间
&gt;&gt; No.
不对
It's time for the students to define and call their own method.
是让学生定义并调用自己的方法的时间
&gt;&gt; Wait, were asking them to define and call a brand new method.
等等 我们让学生定义并调用一个全新的方法
What's it called?
什么方法？
&gt;&gt; It's called create order summary.
名字是 create order summary(创建订单汇总)
It's going to take a summary of everything they entered into the app and
它会包含应用里输入的所有东西
then output that as text.
然后以文本形式输出
&gt;&gt; Do you think they're ready?
你认为它们准备好了吗？
&gt;&gt; I think so.
我认为准备好了
I think it's time for our little birds to spread their wings and fly.
是时候让我们的小鸟展翅翱翔了
[SOUND].
鸟叫声
Now we're going to change the app so it looks like this.
我们把应用修改成这样
If I change the quantity and then hit the order button,
如果我改变 QUANTITY 然后点击 ORDER 按钮
then it prints out a longer summary of the order.
会输出一个很长的订单汇总
This is what will happen in the main activity at a high level.
这会在 MainActivity 的高级阶段发生
When we click on the Order button in the app, we'll call this method,
当点击应用中的 ORDER 按钮时 会调用这个方法
and then inside of this, we're going to call the calculatePrice method.
然后在这里会调用 calculatePrice 方法
We're going to call the method with no input parameters, we're going to
在没有输入参数的情况下 我们调用一下方法
execute these instructions here, and then we're going to return the price.
执行完这些指令之后会返回价格
Once we have the price in the submitOrder method,
只要 submitOrder 方法中有价格
we're going to be able to call the createOrderSummary with that price.
就可以跟价格一起调用 createOrderSummary 方法
So we pass in a price to this method and
所以 我们向方法中传入一个价格
then we execute the instructions inside of it.
然后我们执行方法里边的指令
And then we're going to return the summary text.
然后返回汇总好的文本
And then in these lines of code we can display that summary onto the screen.
然后在这些代码里 我们可以在屏幕上显示汇总
To implement that in code,
为了在代码里执行
we're going to create the Order Summary Method.
我们要创建 OrderSummary 方法
This is a screenshot of what the final app should look like.
这是应用最终版本的截屏
It's the same as what I showed you earlier.
这跟我之前给你们展示的一样
The first task is to create this as a new method in the MainActivity.
第一个任务是在 MainActivity 中创建一个新的方法
The method will be called createOrderSummary.
方法名是 createOrderSummary
It's going to take as input the price of the order,
它会输入订单的价格
which is going to be a number.
价格是一个数字
Then it's going to return this message.
然后返回这些信息
Feel free to use your own name, or any other name.
你可以用你自己的名字或其他任何名字
And make sure that quantity and
根据用户在数量选择器中的选择 确保
total are accurate based on what user selected in the quantity picker.
数量和总量是正确的
Then just add thank you.
加上 Thank you
The second step is to then call this new method from the submitOrder method.
第二步是在 submitOrder 方法中调用新方法
Once you get this string back in the submitOrder method, then go ahead and
从 submitOrder 中取回字符串 继续
display it on the screen like this.
像这样在屏幕上显示它
Check these boxes when you're done.
做完后勾选这两个框